Guide to the Anaconda Copper Mining Company records 1876-1974
Montana Historical Society
- Boston and Montana Consolidated Copper and Silver Mining Company / Reduction Department (Great Falls)
  - Subject File
    - #110 Reverberatory smelting, 1898-1914 (Box-folder 180 / 4)
    - #111-1 Reverberatory furnaces: construction and installation, 1897-1927 (Box-folder 180 / 5)
    - #111-8 Reverberatory furnaces: Carson patent dispute, 1925-1930 (Box-folder 180 / 6-7)
    - #111-8 Reverberatory furnaces: Carson patent dispute [Archives Map Case], 1925-1930 (Oversize-folder 1)
    - #115 Treating copper matte: Thofern and St. Seine "Reactor" process, 1902 (Box-folder 180 / 8)
    - #119 "Master mechanic's log on power houses and machinery", 1900-1909 (Box-folder 180 / 9)
    - #121 "Automatic time clocks or daters", 1907 (Box-folder 180 / 10)
    - #122 "Salaries paid monthly men", 1897-1926 (Box-folder 180 / 11)
    - #122 "Salaries paid monthly men", 1927-1961 (Box-folder 181 / 1-6)
    - #123 "Comparative analyses on converter copper shipped east", 1902-1904 (Box-folder 182 / 1)
    - #124 Labor relations reports, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 182 / 2)
    - #127 Fire insurance policies, 1901-1918 (Box-folder 182 / 3)
    - #128 "Claying converter contracts", 1896-1905 (Box-folder 182 / 4)
    - #132 "Slag casting machine and storage bins", 1898-1912 (Box-folder 182 / 5)
    - #133 "Temporary shutdowns of works on holidays and for general repairs...", 1898-1959 (Box-folder 182 / 6)
    - #134 "Political: working hours for employees voting at elections", 1901-1959 (Box-folder 182 / 7)
    - #142 "Acid linings for Converters", 1897-1911 (Box-folder 182 / 8)
    - #143 "Class I converters and stalls", 1900-1910 (Box-folder 182 / 9)
    - #145 "Converters Lining Department" (includes Clay Mill Department), 1896-1911 (Box-folder 182 / 10)
    - #149 "Complaints regarding quality of copper", 1898-1964 (Box-folder 183 / 1-2)
    - #149-30 "Complaints regarding quality of copper: Rolling Mills Department", 1918-1958 (Box-folder 183 / 3)
    - #150 "Local foundry", 1900-1965 (Box-folder 183 / 4-5)
    - #153 Accident insurance policies, 1898-1914 (Box-folder 183 / 6-8)
    - #153 Accident insurance policies: recreation facilities, 1935-1950 (Box-folder 183 / 9)
    - #155-4 "Chimneys, flues and dust chambers: cave-ins...and cost of repairs", 1899-1963 (Box-folder 184 / 1)
    - #155-17 "Chimneys, flues and dust chambers: treatment of flue dust and...costs", 1904-1968 (Box-folder 184 / 2)
    - #155-24 "Chimneys, flues and dust chambers: flue dust recovery and losses", 1902-1970 (Box-folder 184 / 3)
    - #157 "Vouchers" (re policy, etc.), 1899-1905 (Box-folder 184 / 4)
    - #158 "Treatment records: ore received and production reports", 1904-1914 (Box-folder 184 / 5)
    - #159 Timekeepers' Department, 1902-1970 (Box-folder 184 / 6)
    - #160 "Monthly statements of freight paid", 1931-1939 (Box-folder 184 / 7-8)
    - #161 "Evans-Klepetko automatic gas producers", 1897-1902 (Box-folder 184 / 9-10)
    - #162 "Loomis-Pettibone gas producers", 1900-1901 (Box-folder 184 / 11)
    - #163 "Hot blast stoves for blast furnaces", 1901-1903 (Box-folder 184 / 12)
    - #164 Water tanks and pipe lines (re sewers), 1906-1967 (Box-folder 184 / 13)
    - #167 McDougall and Brueckner Departments, 1894-1924 (Box-folder 185 / 1)
    - #168 Gas Producer Brueckner Department, 1901-1907 (Box-folder 185 / 2)
    - #169 Frank Klepetko, 1898-1909 (Box-folder 185 / 3)
    - #170 "Weekly reports to William Scallon and J.D. Ryan re Great Falls operations", 1902-1906 (Box-folder 185 / 4)
    - #174 Steam superheater, 1893-1907 (Box-folder 185 / 5)
    - #179-1 Blast Furnace Department (re construction and installation), 1898-1921 (Box-folder 185 / 6)
    - #179-3 Blast Furnace Department: "The Development of Blast Furnace Construction at the Boston & Montana Smelter", by J.A. Church, 1913 (Box-folder 185 / 7)
    - #179 Blast Furnace Department, 1897-1934 (Box-folder 185 / 8)
    - #180 Furnace Refinery Department, 1899-1959 (Box-folder 185 / 9-10)
    - #180-40 Furnace Refinery Department: labor conferences, 1942-1966 (Box-folder 185 / 11)
    - #180-41 Furnace Refinery Department: electric loading truck, 1944-1959 (Box-folder 186 / 1)
    - #180-42 Furnace Refinery Department: production of copper billets, 1948-1958 (Box-folder 186 / 2-4)
    - #181 Electrolytic Refinery Department, 1940-1967 (Box-folder 186 / 5-6)
    - #181-31 Electrolytic Refinery Department: tellurium purification, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 186 / 7)
    - #182 Electrolytic solutions: impurities, 1897-1943 (Box-folder 187 / 1-2)
    - #184 "Treatment of electrolytic anode scrap", 1915-1959 (Box-folder 187 / 3)
    - #193 "Contracts for unloading ore, coal, limestone, etc.", 1896-1906 (Box-folder 187 / 4)
    - #195 "Screening and sorting of crude ore for smelting", 1898-1922 (Box-folder 187 / 5)
    - #195 "Screening and sorting of crude ore for smelting: Great Falls", 1910-1914 (Box-folder 187 / 6)
    - #196 "Regulating of B & M ore shipments", 1896-1903 (Box-folder 187 / 7)
    - #197-1 "Sampling and assaying of regular B & M ore shipments at Great Falls", 1901-1912 (Box-folder 187 / 8)
    - #197-2 "Sampling and assaying of regular B & M ore shipments at Great Falls: comparative tests...to determine...moisture loss", 1906-1908 (Box-folder 187 / 9)
    - #197-3 "Sampling and assaying of regular B & M ore shipments at Great Falls: data furnished...re sample ore cars", 1907 (Box-folder 187 / 10)
    - #203 Concentrator Department, 1891-1929 (Box-folder 188 / 1)
    - #205 "Concentrator overflow slime treatment", 1905-1914 (Box-folder 188 / 2)
    - #212 "Prizes given employees for work performed", 1902-1959 (Box-folder 188 / 3)
    - #213 Shops Department, 1913, 1950-1958 (Box-folder 188 / 4)
    - #216 "Inquiries from various outsiders re B & M works", 1900-1970 (Box-folder 188 / 5-7)
    - #216-2 "Inquiries from various outsiders re B & M works: printed forms", 1901-1944 (Box-folder 188 / 8)
    - #216-3 "Inquiries from various outsiders re B & M works: information...for advertising", 1906-1941 (Box-folder 188 / 9)
    - #218-1 Clubs and organizations: golf and tennis, 1898-1950 (Box-folder 188 / 10)
    - #218-2 Clubs and organizations: Rotary Club, 1923-1939 (Box-folder 188 / 11)
    - #218-4 Clubs and organizations: Chamber of Commerce, 1927-1941 (Box-folder 188 / 12)
    - #218-4 Clubs and organizations: Chamber of Commerce, 1942-1970 (Box-folder 189 / 1-2)
    - #218-5 Clubs and organizations: Engineering Club, 1928-1959 (Box-folder 189 / 3)
    - #218-6 Clubs and organizations: miscellaneous, 1931-1964 (Box-folder 189 / 4)
    - #218-7 Clubs and organizations: Junior Chamber of Commerce, 1938-1959 (Box-folder 189 / 5)
    - #219 "Banking", 1902-1955 (Box-folder 189 / 6)
    - #221 "Smelter building ventilation", 1898-1955 (Box-folder 189 / 7)
    - #223 "Scale house, track scales, and weighers", 1900-1962 (Box-folder 189 / 8)
    - #225 Surface Department: Dempster Dumpster, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 189 / 10)
    - #227-1 Laboratory Department: general laboratory, 1901-1957 (Box-folder 189 / 11)
    - #227-4 Laboratory Department: "comparative values of laboratory determinations", 1906-1948 (Box-folder 189 / 12)
    - #227-5 Laboratory Department: umpire assays, 1909-1959 (Box-folder 189 / 13)
    - #227 Laboratory Department: Sunday work, fire loss, new building, seniority, 1903-1965 (Box-folder 189 / 14)
    - #227-13 Laboratory Department: check assaying, 1922-1968 (Box-folder 190 / 1-3)
    - #227-14 Laboratory Department: check assaying, comparison of laboratory methods, 1923-1968 (Box-folder 190 / 4)
    - #229 "Carbon in refined copper", 1899-1900 (Box-folder 190 / 5)
    - #230 "Smoke damage" (re air pollution), 1903-1960 (Box-folder 190 / 6)
    - #230 "Air pollution", 1964-1968 (Box-folder 190 / 7-8)
    - #230-2 "Smoke damage: soil & vegetation samples", 1902-1910 (Box-folder 191 / 1)
    - #230-2 "Smoke damage: soil & vegetation samples" [Archives Map Case], 1902-1910 (Oversize-folder 1)
    - #231 "Slag & tailings disposition", 1900-1954 (Box-folder 191 / 2)
    - #233 "Rental of B & M coal lands", 1897-1918 (Box-folder 191 / 3)
    - #234 "Tests on recovery of material by McDougall roasting", 1903-1910 (Box-folder 191 / 4)
    - #235 "Salaries, expenses, and disbursements of Legal Department", 1901-1967 (Box-folder 191 / 5)
    - #237 Payroll deductions (includes lists of Western Federation of Miners union members), 1895-1943 (Box-folder 191 / 6-8)
    - #237-6 Payroll deductions: Mill and Smelterman's Union, 1898-1961 (Box-folder 191 / 9-10)
    - #237-9 Payroll deductions: other unions, 1908-1910 (Box-folder 191 / 11)
    - #237-11 Payroll deductions: Albright employees, 1911-1916 (Box-folder 191 / 12)
    - #238 Subscriptions: charities, 1900-1957 (Box-folder 192 / 1-3)
    - #238-2 Subscriptions: organizations, 1908-1934 (Box-folder 192 / 4)
    - #238-3 Subscriptions: bronze markers, 1924-1940 (Box-folder 192 / 5)
    - #239 "Use of pulverized coal in reverberatory smelting", 1901-1917 (Box-folder 192 / 6)
    - #239-2 "Use of pulverized coal in reverberatory smelting: construction and installation of #1-2 reverberatory furnace...", 1913-1917 (Box-folder 192 / 7)
    - #240 "Weather observations and instruments (includes daily reports, 1908-1914), 1903-1940, 1952 (Box-folder 192 / 8-9)
    - #241 "Special data for Treasurer Addicks", 1903-1904 (Box-folder 193 / 1)
    - #242 "Callow slime tanks or pulp thickeners", 1904 (Box-folder 193 / 2)
    - #244 "Preservation of timber", 1904-1964 (Box-folder 193 / 3)
    - #245 "Damages due to dumping slag and tailings in river: Ft. Benton water supply" (re water pollution), 1908-1916 (Box-folder 193 / 4-7)
    - #245 "Damages due to dumping slag and tailings in river: Ft. Benton water supply" (re water pollutions) [Archives Map Case], 1908-1916 (Oversize-folder 1)
    - #245-5 "Damages due to dumping slag and tailings in river: William Witt ranch" (re water pollution), 1907-1914 (Box-folder 193 / 8-9)
    - #245-6 "Damages due to dumping slag and tailings in river: Carl Schilling ranch" (re water pollution), 1908-1913 (Box-folder 193 / 10)
    - #245-10 "Damages due to dumping slag and tailings in river: analysis of...water" (re water pollution), 1908-1917 (Box-folder 193 / 11)
    - #245-11 "Damages due to dumping slag and tailings in river: Ft. Benton water supply, daily reports" [sampled] (re water pollution), 1913 (Box-folder 193 / 12)
    - #245-12 "Damages due to dumping slag and tailings in river: construction of reservoir at Ft. Benton" (re water pollution), 1912-1913 (Box-folder 193 / 13)
    - #246 "Superintendent's weekly review of operations", 1905-1913 (Box-folder 194 / 1-8)
    - #246 "Superintendent's weekly review of operations", 1914-1922 (Box-folder 195 / 1-8)
    - #246 "Superintendent's weekly review of operations", 1923-1929 (Box-folder 196 / 1-7)
    - #246 "Superintendent's weekly review of operations", 1939-1969 (Box-folder 197 / 1-2)
    - #247 "Treatment of copper precipitate", 1899-1957 (Box-folder 197 / 3)
    - #249 "Hot & cold solutions at Electrolytic Plant", 1903-1960 (Box-folder 197 / 4)
    - #252 "Arsenic and antimony in anodes", 1913-1965 (Box-folder 197 / 5)
    - #253 "Electrolytic Department costs" (comparison of Great Falls and Raritan), 1943-1966 (Box-folder 197 / 6-7)
    - #255 "Making of starting sheets: aluminum cathodes for Electrolytic Zinc Plant", 1919-1959 (Box-folder 197 / 8)
    - #257 "Blast furnace slag: treatment, losses, analyses, etc.", 1949-1961 (Box-folder 197 / 9)
    - #257-7 "Electric furnaces: electric smelting of lead blast furnace slag & reverberatory zinc slag for recovery of zinc & iron", 1926 (Box-folder 197 / 10)
    - #257-8 "East Helena Slag Treatment Plant", 1926-1927 (Box-folder 197 / 11)
    - #257-8 "East Helena Slag Treatment Plant" [Archives Map Case], 1926-1927 (Oversize-folder 1)
    - #257-8 "East Helena Slag Treatment Plant", 1927-1949 (Box-folder 198 / 1-3)
    - #257-8 "East Helena Slag Treatment Plant" [Archives Map Case], 1927-1949 (Oversize-folder 1)
    - #257-11 "Blast furnace slag: settlements with A.S.A.R. Co.", 1927-1945, 1951-1964 (Box-folder 198 / 4-5)
    - #257-12 "Blast furnace slag: shipment of East Helena fume", 1930-1937 (Box-folder 198 / 6)
    - #258 "Blast furnace smelting", 1893-1944 (Box-folder 198 / 7-8)
    - #258-2 "Blast furnace smelting: air for blast furnaces", 1898-1913 (Box-folder 198 / 9)
    - #258-3 "Blast furnace smelting: water and heat consumption of blast furnace jackets", 1910-1913 (Box-folder 198 / 10)
    - #258-4 "Blast furnace smelting: methods", 1893-1913 (Box-folder 198 / 11)
    - #259 "Blast furnace charge calculations & analyses of charges", 1904-1914 (Box-folder 199 / 1)
    - #260 "Reverberatory charge calculations & analyses of charges", 1903-1914 (Box-folder 199 / 2)
    - #261 "Class II converters and stalls", 1906-1911 (Box-folder 199 / 3)
    - #262 "Inspection trips by B & M officials to outside mills & smelters", 1930-1957 (Box-folder 199 / 4-8)
    - #262 "Inspection trips by B & M officials to outside mills & smelters", 1958-1966 (Box-folder 200 / 1-5)
    - #266 "Richards' pulsator classifiers", 1905-1908 (Box-folder 200 / 6)
    - #266 "Richards' pulsator classifiers", 1909-1917 (Box-folder 201 / 1-2)
    - #266 "Richards' pulsator classifiers: wear in pulsator valves", 1908-1909 (Box-folder 201 / 3)
    - #270 "Manufacture and disposition of bluestone", 1943-1949 (Box-folder 201 / 4)
    - #271 "Method of sampling and preparation of samples: electrolytic and furnace refinery", 1937-1947 (Box-folder 201 / 5)
    - #271-25 "Method of sampling and preparation of samples: Zinc Plant", 1917-1963 (Box-folder 201 / 6-7)
    - #272 "Weighing of Blast Furnace charges", 1905-1916 (Box-folder 201 / 8)
    - #284 "Treatment concentrator slimes", 1903-1914 (Box-folder 201 / 9)
    - #284 "Treatment concentrator slimes [Archives Map Case], 1903-1914 (Oversize-folder 1)
    - #288 "Repairs to company house #2", 1898-1942 (Box-folder 201 / 10)
    - #289 "Repairs to company house #3", 1898-1941 (Box-folder 201 / 11)
    - #300 "Repairs to company house #14", 1919-1961 (Box-folder 201 / 12)
    - #301 "Repairs to company house #15", 1929-1957 (Box-folder 201 / 13)
    - #319 "Silver slime treatment", 1906-1968 (Box-folder 202 / 1)
    - #322 "Concentrator production and loss", 1898-1929 (Box-folder 202 / 2)
    - #324 "Tests on concentrator rolls", 1904-1911 (Box-folder 202 / 3)
    - #326 "McDougall roasting", 1900-1965 (Box-folder 202 / 4)
    - #327 "Minimum and maximum loading", 1893-1967 (Box-folder 202 / 5)
    - #333 "Strikes at Great Falls Works by B & M employees", 1906-1967 (Box-folder 202 / 6)
    - #339 "Methods of drying converter linings", 1906-1911 (Box-folder 202 / 7)
    - #343 "Huntington mills", 1900-1914 (Box-folder 202 / 8)
    - #344 "McLeod revolving screen", 1906-1907 (Box-folder 202 / 9)
    - #345 "Mathewson blast furnace", 1905-1921 (Box-folder 202 / 10)
    - #347 "Converter practice", 1880-1926 (Box-folder 203 / 1)
    - #348 "Reverberatory costs", 1896-1913 (Box-folder 203 / 2)
    - #357 "Losses in overflow slimes and settling of slimes" (includes reports), 1899-1914 (Box-folder 203 / 3-4)
    - #358 "Treatment of Huntington mill product by various systems", 1909-1910 (Box-folder 203 / 5-6)
    - #359 "Production of concentrator slimes", 1905-1911 (Box-folder 203 / 7)
    - #360 "Flow of material in launders and on dump", 1906-1919 (Box-folder 203 / 8)
    - #363 "Evans jigs", 1903-1910 (Box-folder 204 / 1)
    - #364 "Nissen stamp mill", 1906 (Box-folder 204 / 2)
    - #367 "Deister concentrating table", 1906-1918 (Box-folder 204 / 3)
    - #368 "Woodbury bull or dewooding jig", 1906-1911 (Box-folder 204 / 4)
    - #368 "Woodbury bull or dewooding jig" [Archives Map Case], 1906-1911 (Oversize-folder 1)
    - #369 "Laboratory equipment for making physical tests on copper", 1906-1960 (Box-folder 204 / 5)
    - #373 "Repairs and replacing of buildings and equipment at Electrolytic Plant", 1897-1960 (Box-folder 204 / 6)
    - #374 "Repairs and replacing of buildings and equipment at Furnace Refinery", 1907-1959 (Box-folder 204 / 7)
    - #376 "Specification requirements for refined copper", 1898-1959 (Box-folder 204 / 8)
    - #376-2 "Specification requirements for refined copper: instructions...", 1902-1961 (Box-folder 204 / 9)
    - #376-3 "Specification requirements for refined copper: ...American Society for Testing Materials", 1910-1969 (Box-folder 204 / 10)
    - #376-6 "Specification requirements for refined copper: Western Electric Company", 1923-1959 (Box-folder 204 / 11)
    - #379 Deister concentrating tables, 1907-1908 (Box-folder 205 / 1)
    - #381 Humphrey rolls, 1905-1907 (Box-folder 205 / 2)
    - #386 Converter air, 1913 (Box-folder 205 / 3)
    - #390 "Silver and gold in converter anodes", 1946-1968 (Box-folder 205 / 4)
    - #397 Accident insurance claims, 1896-1909 (Box-folder 205 / 5)
    - #429 Ore sampling at Washoe Sampler, 1906-1917 (Box-folder 205 / 6)
    - #430 "Centrifugal concentrators", 1907-1930 (Box-folder 205 / 7)
    - #436 "Hot blast stoves for reverberatory furnaces", 1913-1938 (Box-folder 205 / 8)
    - #437 "Information furnished by B & M Company to outsiders re Richards pulsator classifier and jigs", 1907-1911 (Box-folder 205 / 9)
    - #440 Classifiers, 1903-1941 (Box-folder 205 / 10)
    - #440 Classifiers [Blueprint: Archives Map Case], 1903-1941 (Oversize-folder 1)
    - #441 King screen, 1907 (Box-folder 205 / 11)
    - #447 "Purchase of lands for right-of-way at Black Eagle", 1908-1916 (Box-folder 205 / 12)
    - #450 "Automatic feeding machines", 1902-1914 (Box-folder 205 / 13)
    - #450 "Automatic feeding machines" [Blueprint: Archives Map Case], 1902-1914 (Oversize-folder 1)
    - #451 "Anaconda men employed at Great Falls", 1959-1963 (Box-folder 205 / 14)
    - #453 "Coates' concentrating tube", 1907 (Box-folder 205 / 15)
    - #455 "Class III converters & stalls (Big 7)", 1910-1912 (Box-folder 205 / 16)
    - #457 Cranes, 1895-1925 (Box-folder 205 / 17)
    - #458 Crushers, 1905-1913 (Box-folder 205 / 18)
    - #459 "Erection of chimney by Alphons Custodis Construction Company" (re "Stack") [misc. sub-files #459-1 to 459-20], 1905-1955 (Box-folder 206 / 1-11)
    - #459-3 "Erection of chimney by Alphons Custodis Construction Company" [Blueprint: Archives Map Case], 1905-1955 (Oversize-folder 1)
    - #459-16 "Erection of chimney by Alphons Custodis Construction Company" [Blueprint: Archives Map Case], 1905-1955 (Oversize-folder 1)
    - #461 Richards' sorting tubes, 1908 (Box-folder 206 / 12)
    - #466 "Condensing, settling, and collection of fumes and flue dust", 1966-1968 (Box-folder 206 / 13)
    - #470 blast furnace costs, 1901-1911 (Box-folder 206 / 14)
    - #471 Converter tonnages, 1913-1918 (Box-folder 206 / 15)
    - #474 Slime treatment costs, 1902-1961 (Box-folder 206 / 16)
    - #478 "McDougall production and losses", 1906-1908 (Box-folder 206 / 17)
    - #479 "McDougall calcining costs", 1900-1911 (Box-folder 206 / 18)
    - #487 "Cost of operating concentrating machinery", 1899-1912 (Box-folder 206 / 19)
    - #488 "Speeds of machinery in concentrator", 1900-1912 (Box-folder 207 / 1)
    - #489 "Magnetic concentrating", 1901-1919 (Box-folder 207 / 2)
    - #492 "Electrolytic protection of jig screens from corrosion", 1905 (Box-folder 207 / 3)
    - #493 "Jig and tank plugs", 1904-1909 (Box-folder 207 / 4)
    - #494 "McLeod's trommel spiders", 1903-1907 (Box-folder 207 / 5)
    - #495 "McLeod's bull jig", 1904 (Box-folder 207 / 6)
    - #496 "McLeod's band clutch", 1907-1908 (Box-folder 207 / 7)
    - #499 "Harz jigs", 1903-1912 (Box-folder 207 / 8)
    - #500 "Trommels", 1906-1909 (Box-folder 207 / 9)
    - #502 "General fine concentrates", 1941-1964 (Box-folder 207 / 10)
    - #512 "Scrap lead and lead dross shipments", 1938-1959 (Box-folder 207 / 11)
    - #524 "Information furnished re concentrating", 1906-1926 (Box-folder 207 / 12)
    - #524 "Information furnished re concentrating" [Blueprint: Archives Map Case], 1906-1926 (Oversize-folder 1)
    - #528 "Ownership of property adjacent to B & M Works" (re Riverside Addition, Kittinger property), 1905-1936 (Box-folder 207 / 13)
    - #529 "Reverberatory production and loss", 1896-1905 (Box-folder 207 / 14)
    - #534 Brick Department: clay and shale lands, 1913-1961 (Box-folder 207 / 15)
    - #535 "Sonstadt solution", 1908 (Box-folder 207 / 16)
    - #540 "Slippage of blast furnace blowers", 1903-1907 (Box-folder 207 / 17)
    - #541 "Taxes on B & M property", 1909-1940 (Box-folder 207 / 18-19)
    - #541 "Taxes on B & M property", 1941-1968 (Box-folder 208 / 1-2)
    - #544 "Railroad equipment lists", 1944-1962 (Box-folder 208 / 3)
    - #564 Electrical Shop, 1907-1959 (Box-folder 208 / 4)
    - #566 Refining tanks: lining, 1906-1961 (Box-folder 208 / 5)
    - #566 Refining tanks: lining [Blueprint: Archives Map Case], 1906-1961 (Oversize-folder 1)
    - #568 "Gas producer tests", 1910-1911 (Box-folder 208 / 6)
    - #576 Patents: converter furnaces, 1902-1915 (Box-folder 208 / 7)
    - #577 "Methods of assaying copper precipitate", 1908 (Box-folder 208 / 8)
    - #583 "Employees", 1936-1944 (Box-folder 208 / 9)
    - #583-7 "Employees: sickness or injury away from work", 1942-1946 (Box-folder 208 / 10)
    - #585 "Contracts with hospitals and doctors" (includes reports), 1891-1915 (Box-folder 208 / 11)
    - #585 "Contracts with hospitals and doctors" (includes reports), 1931-1955 (Box-folder 209 / 1-6)
    - #585 "Contracts with hospitals and doctors" (miscellaneous files), 1898-1959 (Box-folder 210 / 1)
    - #586 Telephone system, 1900-1922 (Box-folder 210 / 2)
    - #587 "Methods of lining converters", 1905-1924 (Box-folder 210 / 3)
    - #587 "Methods of lining converters" [Blueprint: Archives Map Case], 1905-1924 (Oversize-folder 2)
    - #592 "Anode shipments from Washoe Reduction Works", 1915-1929 (Box-folder 210 / 4)
    - #593 "Letters of inquiry and recommendation", 1932-1942 (Box-folder 210 / 5)
    - #600 "Scale of wages paid by B & M and other companies" (re different unions), 1915-1917 (Box-folder 210 / 6)
    - #600-10 "Scale of wages paid by B & M and other companies: instructions re changes in classification and rates of labor", 1912-1923 (Box-folder 210 / 7)
    - #600-20 "Scale of wages paid by B & M and other companies" (classification and rates), 1918-1944 (Box-folder 210 / 8-11)
    - #600-34 "Scale of wages paid by B & M and other companies" (classification and rates), 1944-1964 (Box-folder 211 / 1-2)
    - #601-1 "Handling of accidents to employees: B & M Reduction Works", 1908-1964 (Box-folder 211 / 3)
    - #601-2 "Handling of accidents to employees: Albright Quarries", 1911-1912 (Box-folder 211 / 4)
    - #601-4 "Handling of accidents to employees: Employers' Liability & Workmen's Compensation Law...", 1915-1959 (Box-folder 211 / 5)
    - #601-5 "Handling of accidents to employees: Employers' Liability & Workmen's Compensation bills (proposed)", 1910-1961 (Box-folder 211 / 6)
    - #601-6 "Handling of accidents to employees: Armington Clay Mine", 1922-1935 (Box-folder 211 / 7)
    - #601-7 "Handling of accidents to employees" (re compensation reserve), 1925-1964 (Box-folder 211 / 8-9)
    - #602 "Treatment costs on copper precipitate", 1906-1909 (Box-folder 212 / 1)
    - #602 "Treatment costs on copper precipitate" [Blueprint: Archives Map Case], 1906-1909 (Oversize-folder 2)
    - #606 "Converter anodes", 1908-1960 (Box-folder 212 / 2)
    - #608 "United States Land Office reports" (includes lists of homestead entries), 1895-1896 (Box-folder 212 / 3)
    - #609 "Precipitate slime", 1908-1909 (Box-folder 212 / 4)
    - #611 Carpenter Shop, 1900-1959 (Box-folder 212 / 5)
    - #612-1 Machine Shop, 1908-1953 (Box-folder 212 / 6)